Love on Ice is a romance, drama, tv movie film directed by Bradley Walsh.
Emily James, now 27 years old and considered a relic in the world of figure skating, gets an
improbably shot to reclaim skating glory when a young coach sees greatness in her.
Together, they find their love of skating goes beyond the ice.
Spencer Patterson, played by Andrew W. Walker.
Mia Lee, played by Gail O'Grady.
Emily James, played by Julie Berman.
Leslie Adams, played by Kate Drummond.
Lindsey Tuttle, played by Ipsita Paul.
Nikki Lee, played by Ana Golja.
Ice Cream Man is a 1995 American direct-to-video black comedy horror film produced and directed by Paul Norman, a director
of pornographic films (under the pseudonym "Norman Apstein"), and written by Sven Davison and David Dobkin.
The film stars Clint Howard, Olivia Hussey, Jan-Michael
Vincent, David Warner and David Naughton.
The film's plot follows a deranged man who was recently released from a psychiatric institution
and opens up an ice cream factory where he begins using human flesh in his recipes.
The film had an estimated $2 million budget.
It was released at Chicago's Brew and View for the Clint Howard Film Festival in 1995, on
DVD on October 19, 2004, and on Blu-ray and DVD by Vinegar Syndrome in 2017.
The tone is emotional.